directphoneshop.co.uk 2013-04-13

# Privacy Policy - Direct Phone Shop

**Home Page** » Privacy Policy

The concept of privacy holds a paramount place in today's scenario henceforth; we envisage certain privacy policy, so that the personal and other information can be preserved. We endeavour to take all efforts which are required for maintaining online privacy norms on up-to-date basis which shows you the way towards safe and secured transactions. ****  

**1\. Purpose of this policy:** The purpose of this policy is:

  * to assure you that we recognise and fully respect the privacy and personal data of the visitors to this website and
  * to explain what personal information we collect from this website and how we ensure its' best protection.

By your access to and use of this website you agree to our processing, storing and using that information in accordance with the principles set out in this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Collection of Information:** We will limit the collection and use of your information to a minimum. We will only collect such information when you register for any of our services or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may also collect information to inform you about the products and services offered by us or our associates. We may use cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use our services in order to improve the quality of our services.   
We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. We will only collect such information as is required to help you avail the services or keeping you informed about the products and services offered by us or our associates.

**3\. Uses of Information:** We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services. We may also share information with third parties, subject to your prior consent and without consent in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

The information you provide may also be used for analytical and statistical purposes.

**4\. Disclosure of Information:** We do not share, sell or rent your e-mail, postal address or any other data we hold about you to any third party, unless a prior consent is obtained from you. We may however disclose your personal information as and when required under law, in cases where it is obligatory to do so.

We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

**5\. Security of Information:** We will take all reasonable steps to safeguard the security and confidentiality of any information you provide to us. We cannot however guarantee the security of any information you disclose online. You accept the inherent security implications of providing information over the Internet and will not hold us responsible for any breach of security or disclosure of information unless we have been negligent. Your personal information will be preserved wherever it is mandatory to do so and for this purpose adequate steps will be pursued to shield the personal information from unlawful access.

**6\. Access to collected information:** We provide site users with access to all information that we maintain about them, including transaction and contact information upon proper verification. The same can be provided to you on request, in case you experience any doubts.

**7\. Cookies:** To facilitate your use of our website and to collect aggregate information, we may use “cookies”. To view our Cookie Policy, please ** _click_** ** _here_**.

**8\. Changes to Privacy Policy:** We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time. If this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with others.

**9\. Consent:** By using this website you consent to the collection and use of your personal information in the manner set out above.

**10\. More Information:** If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy or require any further information please send your request by email to: ** ** [info@directphoneshop.co.uk](mailto:info@directphoneshop.co.uk)
